<form>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.Enabled</id>
        <label>Enabled</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enable the APC UPS service.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.UPSName</id>
        <label>UPS name</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Use this to give your UPS a name in logfiles.]]></help>
        <hint>Must be less than 8 characters in length.</hint>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.UPSCable</id>
        <label>UPS cable type</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Defines the type of cable connecting the UPS to the server.]]></help>
        <hint>Choose cable type.</hint>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.UPSType</id>
        <label>UPS Type</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Corresponds to the type of UPS in use.]]></help>
        <hint>You will also need to select the UPS Device.</hint>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.Device</id>
        <label>UPS Device</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Which port is the UPS connected to. Leave blank for USB UPSes.<br>Default: /dev/cuaU0]]></help>
        <hint>Specify an appropriate port or address. default: /dev/cuaU0</hint>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.Netserver</id>
        <label>Netserver</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the state of the network information server.]]></help>
        <hint>A network information server is available to retrieve the STATUS and EVENT data over the network.</hint>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.NetserverAddress</id>
        <label>Netserver IP address</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[IP address on which the Netserver will listen for incoming connections.]]></help>
        <hint>Default address is 0.0.0.0 which means any incoming connection will be serviced.</hint>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.NetserverPort</id>
        <label>Netserver port</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Network port used to send STATUS and EVENT data over the network.]]></help>
        <hint>Port 3551 is the default as registered with the IANA.</hint>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.Polltime</id>
        <label>Polltime</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Interval, in seconds, at which apcupsd polls the UPS for the current state.]]></help>
        <hint>This setting applies to both directly attached units - type: apcsmart, usb, dumb, and networked units - type: net, snmp.</hint>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.OnBatteryDelay</id>
        <label>OnBattery Delay</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Time in seconds from when a power failure is detected until we react to it with an on battery event (Default: 6).]]></help>
        <hint>This means that, apccontrol will be called with the powerout argument immediately when a power failure is detected.  However, the onbattery argument is passed to apccontrol only after the ONBATTERYDELAY time.  If you don't want to be annoyed by short powerfailures, make sure that apccontrol powerout does nothing.</hint>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.BatteryLevel</id>
        <label>Battery Level</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[If during a power failure, the remaining battery percentage (as reported by the UPS) is below or equal to BATTERYLEVEL,  apcupsd will initiate a system shutdown.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.Minutes</id>
        <label>Minutes</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[If during a power failure, the remaining runtime in minutes (as calculated internally by the UPS) is below or equal to MINUTES,apcupsd, will initiate a system shutdown.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.Timeout</id>
        <label>Minutes</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[If during a power failure, the UPS has run on batteries for TIMEOUT many seconds or longer, apcupsd will initiate a system shutdown. A value of 0 disables this timer.]]></help>
        <hint>Note, if you have a Smart UPS, you will most likely want to disable this timer by setting it to zero. That way, your UPS will continue on batteries until either the PERCENT charge remaing drops to or below BATTERYLEVEL, or the remaining battery runtime drops to or below MINUTES.  Of course, if you are testing, setting this to 60 causes a quick system shutdown if you pull the power plug. If you have an older dumb UPS, you will want to set this to less than the time you know you can run on batteries.</hint>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.Annoy</id>
        <label>Annoy</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Time in seconds between annoying users to signoff prior to system shutdown. 0 disables.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.AnnoyDelay</id>
        <label>Annoy Delay</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Initial delay after power failure before warning users to get off the system.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.KillDelay</id>
        <label>Kill Delay</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[If KILLDELAY is non-zero, apcupsd will continue running after a shutdown has been requested, and after the specified time in seconds attempt to kill the power.

          This is for use on systems where apcupsd cannot regain control after a shutdown.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.UPSClass</id>
        <label>UPS Class</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Normally standalone unless you share an UPS using an APC ShareUPS card.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.UPSMode</id>
        <label>UPS Mode</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Normally disable unless you share an UPS using an APC ShareUPS card.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>apcupsd.general.NoLogon</id>
        <label>Nologon Mode</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[The condition which determines when users are prevented from logging in during a power failure.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
</form>
