<form>
    <field>
        <id>reverse.enabled</id>
        <label>Enabled</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enable this domain.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>reverse.FromDomain</id>
        <label>Domain</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>example.com</hint>
        <help><![CDATA[Enter a domain name. For a base domain, use "example.com" or "opn.example.com". Using a base domain enables automatic "Let's Encrypt" and "ZeroSSL" certificates by default. For a wildcard domain, use "*.example.com". Only use wildcard domains with wildcard certificates, which require a DNS Provider. Adding a wildcard domain and pressing "Apply" will activate the "Subdomain" Tab, in which subdomains can be configured.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>reverse.FromPort</id>
        <label>Port</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>443</hint>
        <help><![CDATA[Leave empty to use ports 80 and 443 with automatic redirection from HTTP to HTTPS or choose a custom port. Don't forget to allow these ports with a Firewall rule. If the default ports have been changed in "General Settings", leaving this empty will use the chosen alternative ports instead.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>reverse.description</id>
        <label>Description</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enter a description for this domain.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <type>header</type>
        <label>DNS</label>
        <collapse>true</collapse>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>reverse.DynDns</id>
        <label>Dynamic DNS</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enable or disable Dynamic DNS. Requires a "DNS Provider" in "General Settings". The DNS records of this domain will be automatically updated.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <type>header</type>
        <label>Trust</label>
        <collapse>true</collapse>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>reverse.DisableTls</id>
        <label>Disable TLS</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Disable HTTP over TLS (HTTPS) for this domain. When disabling TLS, automatic certificate management will be disabled and all traffic to and from this domain will be unencrypted.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>reverse.DnsChallenge</id>
        <label>DNS-01 Challenge</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enable the DNS-01 challenge for this domain. Requires a "DNS Provider" in "General Settings". This is mostly only needed for wildcard domains, or when the HTTP-01 and TLS-ALPN-01 challenge can not be used due to restrictive firewall policies.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>reverse.AcmePassthrough</id>
        <label>HTTP-01 Challenge Redirection</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enter a domain name or IP address. The HTTP-01 challenge will be redirected to that destination. This enables an ACME Client behind Caddy to serve "/.well-known/acme-challenge/" on port 80. Caddy will reverse proxy the HTTP-01 challenge for this domain, and will still issue a certificate using the TLS-ALPN-01 challenge or DNS-01 challenge for itself. This option can be used for High Availability when using Caddy with a master and backup OPNsense.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>reverse.CustomCertificate</id>
        <label>Custom Certificate</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Choose a custom certificate from "System - Trust - Certificates" for this domain. Make sure the full chain has been imported.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <type>header</type>
        <label>Access</label>
        <collapse>true</collapse>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>reverse.accesslist</id>
        <label>Access List</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Select an Access List to restrict access to this domain. If unset, any local or remote client is allowed access.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>reverse.basicauth</id>
        <label>Basic Auth</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <size>5</size>
        <help><![CDATA[Select Users to restrict access to this domain. Basic Auth matches after Access Lists. If unset, any user is allowed access. When using CrowdSec, authorization failures will result in automatic bans.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>reverse.AccessLog</id>
        <label>HTTP Access Log</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enable HTTP request logging for this domain and its subdomains. This option is mostly used for troubleshooting, audits and CrowdSec. It will log every single request.]]></help>
    </field>
</form>
