<form>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.DynDnsIpVersions</id>
        <label>DynDns IP Version</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Select the DynDns IP Version: "IPv4+IPv6" to set IPv4 A-Records and IPv6 AAAA-Records, "IPv4 only" for only A-Records, "IPv6 only" for only AAAA-Records.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.DynDnsUpdateOnly</id>
        <label>DynDns Update Only</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[If enabled, no new DNS records will be created. Only existing records will be updated. This means that the A or AAAA records need to be created manually ahead of time.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.DynDnsInterval</id>
        <label>DynDns Check Interval</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>1800</hint>
        <help><![CDATA[Set the interval in seconds to poll for changes in the IP address. Leave empty to use system defaults.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.DynDnsTtl</id>
        <label>DynDns TTL</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Set the TTL (Time to Live) for DNS records in seconds. Leave empty to use the default of an already existing TTL (when updating only) or the default of the provider API (when creating new records). If explicitely set, values should be as defined in rfc2181 section 8.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <type>header</type>
        <label>Additional Checks</label>
        <collapse>true</collapse>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.DynDnsSimpleHttp</id>
        <label>DynDns Check Http</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enter a URL to test the current IP address of the firewall via the HTTP protocol. This is generally not needed as Caddy uses default providers to test the current IP addresses. If a custom provider is preferred, enter the "https://" link to an IP address testing website.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.DynDnsInterface</id>
        <label>DynDns Check Interface</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Select an interface to extract the current IP addresses of the firewall. This is generally not needed as Caddy uses default providers to test the current IP addresses. Depending on the specified DynDns IP Version, at most one IPv6 Global Unicast Address and one IPv4 non-RFC1918 Address will be extracted.]]></help>
    </field>
</form>
