<form>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.enabled</id>
        <label>Enabled</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enable or disable the Caddy web server.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsEmail</id>
        <label>ACME Email</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>info@example.com</hint>
        <help><![CDATA[Enter the email address for certificate notifications.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsAutoHttps</id>
        <label>Auto HTTPS</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Select the auto HTTPS option. "On" (default) creates automatic certificates using Let's Encrypt or ZeroSSL without needing any configuration.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.accesslist</id>
        <label>Trusted Proxies</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Select an Access List of Trusted Proxies. If Caddy is not the first server being connected to by your clients (for example when a CDN is in front of Caddy), you may configure trusted_proxies with a list of IP ranges (CIDRs) from which incoming requests are trusted to have sent good values for these headers. Additionally, set the same Access List to the Domains your Trusted Proxy connects to.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.abort</id>
        <label>Abort Connections</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Abort all connections that don't have a matching handle or access list. This option doesn't conflict with Let's Encrypt. Disable it for troubleshooting purposes, e.g., testing if the Reverse Proxy Domain works and the Certificate has been installed. For production use, enabling this option is recommended.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.GracePeriod</id>
        <label>Grace Period</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>10</hint>
        <help><![CDATA[Defines the grace period for shutting down HTTP servers (i.e. during config changes or when Caddy is stopping) in seconds. During the grace period, no new connections are accepted, idle connections are closed, and active connections are impatiently waited upon to finish their requests. If clients do not finish their requests within the grace period, the server will be forcefully terminated to allow the reload to complete and free up resources. This can influence how long "Apply" of new configurations take, since Caddy waits for all open connections to close.]]></help>
    </field>
</form>
