<form>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.enabled</id>
        <label>Enabled</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enable or disable the Caddy web server.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.EnableLayer4</id>
        <label>(Feature Preview) Enable Layer4</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enable Layer4 support to stream TCP/UDP. WARNING: This feature is in active developement and the configuration can break or change in the future. The Layer4 app matches before the HTTP app. Deactivating this option will remove all Layer4 functionality completely. More information: https://github.com/mholt/caddy-l4]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.HttpPort</id>
        <label>HTTP Port</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>80</hint>
        <help><![CDATA[If the default HTTP port is changed to e.g. 8080, then a port forward from port 80 to 8080 is necessary to issue automatic certificates with the HTTP-01 challenge and serve clients the reverse proxied resources.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.HttpsPort</id>
        <label>HTTPS Port</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>443</hint>
        <help><![CDATA[If the default HTTPS port is changed to e.g. 8443, then a port forward from port 443 to 8443 is necessary to issue automatic certificates with the TLS-ALPN-01 challenge and serve clients the reverse proxied resources.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.DisableSuperuser</id>
        <label>Disable Superuser</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Run this service as "www" user and group, instead of "root". This setting increases security, but comes with the hard restriction that the well-known port range can not be used anymore. After enabling and saving this setting, the service has to be totally restarted. For this, please disable Caddy and press Apply. Afterwards enable Caddy and press Apply. This setting is reversible by following the same steps.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsEmail</id>
        <label>ACME Email</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>info@example.com</hint>
        <help><![CDATA[Enter the email address for certificate notifications. This is required to receive automatic certificates from "Let's Encrypt" and "ZeroSSL".]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsAutoHttps</id>
        <label>Auto HTTPS</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Select the Auto HTTPS option. "On (default)" creates automatic certificates using "Let's Encrypt" or "ZeroSSL". "Off" turns all automatic certificate requests off.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.accesslist</id>
        <label>Trusted Proxies</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Select an Access List to set IP ranges of Trusted Proxies. If Caddy is not the first server being connected to by clients (for example, when a "CDN" is in front of Caddy), configure "Trusted Proxies" with a list of IP ranges (CIDRs) from which incoming requests are trusted to have sent good values for these headers. Additionally, set the same Access List to the domains the Trusted Proxies connect to.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.abort</id>
        <label>Abort Connections</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Abort all connections that don't have a matching Handle or Access List. This option does not conflict with "Let's Encrypt" or "ZeroSSL". Disable it for troubleshooting purposes, e.g., testing if the "Domain" works and the automatic certificate has been installed. For production use, enabling this option is recommended.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.GracePeriod</id>
        <label>Grace Period</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>10</hint>
        <help><![CDATA[Defines the grace period for shutting down Caddy during a reload in seconds. During the grace period, no new connections are accepted, idle connections are closed, and active connections are impatiently waited upon to finish their requests. If clients do not finish their requests within the grace period, the server will be forcefully terminated to allow the reload to complete and free up resources. This can influence how long "Apply" of new configurations take, since Caddy waits for all open connections to close.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
</form>
