<form>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.enabled</id>
        <label>Enabled</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[<strong>Enable or disable the Caddy web server.</strong>]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsEmail</id>
        <label>ACME Email</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>info@example.com</hint>
        <help><![CDATA[<strong>Enter the email address for certificate notifications.</strong> This is <strong>required</strong> to receive automatic certificates from <em>Let's Encrypt</em> and <em>ZeroSSL</em>.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsAutoHttps</id>
        <label>Auto HTTPS</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[<strong>Select the Auto HTTPS option.</strong> <code>On (default)</code> creates automatic certificates using <em>Let's Encrypt</em> or <em>ZeroSSL</em>. <code>Off</code> turns all automatic certificate requests off.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.accesslist</id>
        <label>Trusted Proxies</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[<strong>Select an Access List to set IP ranges of Trusted Proxies.</strong> If Caddy is not the first server being connected to by clients (for example, when a <em>CDN</em> is in front of Caddy), configure <code>Trusted Proxies</code> with a list of IP ranges (CIDRs) from which incoming requests are trusted to have sent good values for these headers. Additionally, set the same <code>Access List</code> to the domains the <code>Trusted Proxies</code> connect to.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.abort</id>
        <label>Abort Connections</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[<strong>Abort all connections that don't have a matching Handle or Access List.</strong> This option does not conflict with <em>Let's Encrypt or ZeroSSL</em>. Disable it for troubleshooting purposes, e.g., testing if the <code>Domain</code> works and the automatic certificate has been installed. <strong>For production use, enabling this option is recommended.</strong>]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.GracePeriod</id>
        <label>Grace Period</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>10</hint>
        <help><![CDATA[<strong>Defines the grace period for shutting down Caddy during a reload in seconds.</strong> During the grace period, no new connections are accepted, idle connections are closed, and active connections are <em>impatiently waited upon</em> to finish their requests. If clients do not finish their requests within the grace period, the server will be <strong>forcefully terminated</strong> to allow the reload to complete and free up resources. This can influence how long <code>Apply</code> of new configurations take, since Caddy waits for all open connections to close.]]></help>
    </field>
</form>
