<form>
    <field>
        <id>domain.enabled</id>
        <label>Enabled</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>This will enable or disable this zone.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.domainname</id>
        <label>Zone Name</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Set the name for this zone. Both forward and reverse zones may be specified, i.e. example.com or 0.168.192.in-addr.arpa.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.allowtransfer</id>
        <label>Allow Transfer</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <help>Define the ACLs where you allow which server can retrieve this zone.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.allowquery</id>
        <label>Allow Query</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <help>Define the ACLs where you allow which client are allowed to query this zone.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.allowrndcupdate</id>
        <label>Allow RDNC key update</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Allow updates via the RDNC key named "rndc-key". The key is shown in the general tab.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.ttl</id>
        <label>TTL</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Set the general Time To Live for this zone.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.refresh</id>
        <label>Refresh Time</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Set the time in seconds after which name servers should refresh the zone information.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.retry</id>
        <label>Retry Time</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Set the time in seconds after which name servers should retry requests if the master does not respond.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.expire</id>
        <label>Expire Time</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Set the time in seconds after which name servers should stop answering requests if the master does not respond.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.negative</id>
        <label>Negative TTL</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Set the time in seconds after which an entry for a non-existent record should expire from cache.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.mailadmin</id>
        <label>Mail Admin</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Set the mail address of zone admin. A @-sign will automatically be replaced with a dot in the zone data.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.dnsserver</id>
        <label>DNS Server</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Set the DNS server hosting this file. This should usually be the FQDN of your firewall where the BIND plugin is installed.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.allowddnsupdate</id>
        <label>Allow DDNS Updates from a dhcp server</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>This will enable a ddns updates from a dhcp-server for this zone (key defined in "General").</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>domain.rpzzone</id>
        <label>Use zone as RPZ (response policy zone)</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>This will enable add this zone as RPZ zone. DNSBL > Enable DNSBL and RPZ has to be enabled for this to work.</help>
    </field>
</form>
