<form>
    <field>
        <type>header</type>
        <label>General Settings</label>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>ndpproxy.general.enabled</id>
        <label>Enable</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Enable or disable this service.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <type>header</type>
        <label>Proxy Settings</label>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>ndpproxy.general.upstream</id>
        <label>Upstream interface</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Choose the upstream interface which receives the external IPv6 prefix from the ISP. Usually, this is the WAN interface. Ethernet interfaces are fully supported, point-to-point (PPPoE) devices are experimental.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>ndpproxy.general.downstream</id>
        <label>Downstream interfaces</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <help>Choose one or multiple downstream interfaces which should proxy the upstream IPv6 prefix. Only ethernet interfaces are supported.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>ndpproxy.general.ra</id>
        <label>Proxy router advertisements</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Proxy upstream RAs to downstream interfaces. Disable this if you use your own RA daemon.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>ndpproxy.general.routes</id>
        <label>Install host routes</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Automatically create host routes for discovered clients. Disabling this means you must manually handle all routing decisions.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <type>header</type>
        <label>Performance Settings</label>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>ndpproxy.general.cache_ttl</id>
        <label>Neighbor cache lifetime</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>10</hint>
        <help>Neighbor cache lifetime in minutes. This controls when stale clients, host routes and firewall aliases are cleaned up. When using a point-to-point interface as upstream, increasing this lifetime is necessary to not prematurely clean up routes.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>ndpproxy.general.cache_max</id>
        <label>Max learned neighbors</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>4096</hint>
        <help>Maximum learned neighbors, increase for large networks.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>ndpproxy.general.cache_file</id>
        <label>Neighbor cache file</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Persist cache to file on service stop and load it on service start. Only neighbors with a valid cache lifetime are loaded. This helps on system reboots to minimize downtime of individual clients.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>ndpproxy.general.route_qps</id>
        <label>Max route operations</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>50</hint>
        <help>Maximum route operations per second. Limits how fast routes are applied; excess operations are queued, not dropped.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>ndpproxy.general.pf_qps</id>
        <label>Max alias operations</label>
        <tYpe>text</type>
        <hint>50</hint>
        <help>Maximum firewall alias operations per second. Limits how fast aliases are populated; excess operations are queued, not dropped.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>ndpproxy.general.pcap_timeout</id>
        <label>Packet capture timeout</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>50</hint>
        <help>Controls CPU usage vs. NDP responsiveness. Lower values (e.g., 25 ms) minimize latency during cache refresh at the cost of more CPU. Higher values (100–250 ms) reduce CPU use but may introduce small latency spikes.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>ndpproxy.general.debug</id>
        <label>Debug log</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Enable debug logging.</help>
    </field>
</form>
