<form>
    <field>
        <id>server.enabled</id>
        <label>Enabled</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Enable this server.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.name</id>
        <label>Name or Prefix</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Name to identify a static server. When creating a server template, then this prefix is used for the server names to be built.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.description</id>
        <label>Description</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Description for this server.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.type</id>
        <label>Type</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Either configure a static server or a template to initialize multiple servers with shared parameters.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <label>Static Server</label>
        <type>header</type>
        <style>table_server_type table_server_type_static</style>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.address</id>
        <label>FQDN or IP</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Provide either the FQDN or the IP address of this server.]]></help>
        <hint>Enter server address.</hint>
    </field>
    <field>
        <label>Server Template</label>
        <type>header</type>
        <style>table_server_type table_server_type_template</style>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.serviceName</id>
        <label>Service Name or FQDN</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Provide either the FQDN for all the servers this template initializes or a service name to discover the available services via DNS SRV records.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.number</id>
        <label>Number of Servers</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[The number of servers this template initializes, i.e. 5 or 1-5.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.linkedResolver</id>
        <label>Resolvers</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Specify the resolver that the server template should look at to discover available services via DNS.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.resolverOpts</id>
        <label>Resolver Options</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <style>tokenize</style>
        <allownew>true</allownew>
        <help><![CDATA[Add resolver options. Use TAB key to complete typing.]]></help>
        <hint>Type option name or choose from list.</hint>
    </field>
    <field>
        <label>UNIX Socket</label>
        <type>header</type>
        <style>table_server_type table_server_type_unix</style>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.unix_socket</id>
        <label>Frontend (Socket Origin)</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Select the frontend that provides the UNIX socket. This UNIX socket will be used as the server's address, making it possible to send connections to this frontend. Only frontends that provide the unix@ pattern as listen address can be selected.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <label>Common Options</label>
        <type>header</type>
        <style>table_server_type table_server_type_static table_server_type_template</style>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.port</id>
        <label>Port</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Provide the TCP or UDP communication port for this server, i.e. 80 or 443. If set, all connections will be sent to this port. If unset, the same port the client connected to will be used.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.mode</id>
        <label>Mode</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the operation mode to use for this server.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.multiplexer_protocol</id>
        <label>Multiplexer Protocol</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Forces the multiplexer's protocol to use for the outgoing connections to this server. It must be compatible with the mode of the backend (TCP or HTTP). It must also be usable on the backend side. Idea behind this option is to bypass the selection of the best multiplexer's protocol for all connections established to this server. Use only when strictly necessary.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.resolvePrefer</id>
        <label>Prefer IP Family</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[When DNS resolution is enabled for a server and multiple IP addresses from different families are returned, HAProxy will prefer using an IP address from the selected family.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.ssl</id>
        <label>SSL</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enable or disable SSL communication with this server.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.sslSNI</id>
        <label>SSL SNI</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[The host name sent in the SNI TLS extension to the server.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.sslVerify</id>
        <label>Verify SSL Certificate</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[If disabled, server certificate is not verified. Otherwise the certificate provided by the server is verified using CAs and optional CRLs. <b>Please note that this setting can be overriden by the global configuration.</b><br/><div class="text-info"><b>NOTE:</b> It is critically important to verify server certificates when using SSL to connect to servers, otherwise the communication is prone to trivial man-in-the-middle attacks rendering SSL totally useless.</div>]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.sslCA</id>
        <label>SSL Verify CA</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <allownew>true</allownew>
        <help><![CDATA[The selected CAs will be used to verify the server certificate. When nothing is selected, the system-wide CA certificate bundle will be used. <br/>To import additional CAs, go to <a href="/system_camanager.php">Authority Manager</a>.]]></help>
        <hint>Type CA name or choose from list.</hint>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.sslCRL</id>
        <label>SSL Verify CRL</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[This certificate revocation list will be used to verify server's certificate. <br/>To import additional CRLs, go to <a href="/system_certmanager.php">Certificate Manager</a>.]]></help>
        <hint>Type CRL name or choose from list.</hint>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.sslClientCertificate</id>
        <label>SSL Client Certificate</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[This certificate will be sent if the server send a client certificate request.<br/>To import additional certificates, go to <a href="/system_certmanager.php">Certificate Manager</a>.]]></help>
        <hint>Type certificate name or choose from list.</hint>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.maxConnections</id>
        <label>Max Connections</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximal number of concurrent connections that will be sent to this server. The default value is "0" which means unlimited.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.weight</id>
        <label>Weight</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Adjust the server's weight relative to other servers.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.checkInterval</id>
        <label>Check Interval</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the interval (in milliseconds) for running health checks on this server. This setting takes precedence over default values in health monitors. It can still be overwritten from the backend pool.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.checkDownInterval</id>
        <label>Down Interval</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the interval (in milliseconds) for running health checks on the server when the server state is DOWN. If it is not set HAProxy uses the check interval.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.checkport</id>
        <label>Port to check</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Provide the TCP communication port to use during check, i.e. 80 or 443.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.source</id>
        <label>Source address</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the source address which will be used when connecting to the server.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>server.advanced</id>
        <label>Option pass-through</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[A list of parameters that will be appended to the server line in every backend where this server will be used.<br/>Example: send-proxy<br/>.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
</form>
