<form>
    <field>
        <label>Global Parameters</label>
        <type>header</type>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.root</id>
        <label>Run as root</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enable or disable HAProxy running as user root. Enabling this option is strongly discouraged.<br/><div class="text-info"><b>NOTE:</b> Running as user root could be a security issue but it may be required by some features.</div>]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.nbthread</id>
        <label>HAProxy threads</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Number of threads to create for each HAProxy process.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.maxConnections</id>
        <label>Maximum connections</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the maximum number of concurrent connections per HAProxy process.<br/><div class="text-info"><b>NOTE:</b> Consider raising the settings for kern.maxfiles and kern.maxfilesperproc in <a target="_blank" href="/system_advanced_sysctl.php">System: Settings: Tunables</a>, otherwise HAProxy will fail to open the specified number of connections.</div>]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.resolversPrefer</id>
        <label>DNS prefer IP family</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[This option allows to choose which IP family is preferred when resolving DNS names. This is useful when IPv6 or IPv4 is not available. It solves a common issue with OCSP updates.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.sslServerVerify</id>
        <label>Verify SSL Server Certificates</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[This enforces a certain behavior for SSL verify on servers, ignoring per-server settings. If set to 'enforce verify', server certificates are verified. If set to 'disable verify', server certificates are not verified. The default is 'no preference' to only use per-server configurations and not enforce a global default for all servers.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.maxDHSize</id>
        <label>Maximum SSL DH Size</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the maximum size of the Diffie-Hellman parameters used for generating the ephemeral/temporary Diffie-Hellman key in case of DHE key exchange (default is 1024).<br/><div class="text-info"><b>NOTE:</b> Higher values will increase the CPU load. For more information about the "tune.ssl.default-dh-param" option please see the HAProxy Documentation.</div>]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.bufferSize</id>
        <label>Buffer size</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Change the buffer size (in bytes). Lower values allow more sessions to coexist in the same amount of RAM, and higher values allow some applications with very large cookies to work. The default value is 16384. <br/><div class="text-info"><b>NOTE:</b> It is strongly recommended not to change this from the default value, as very low values will break some services such as statistics, and values larger than default size will increase memory usage, possibly causing the system to run out of memory.</div>]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.luaMaxMem</id>
        <label>Maximum RAM per LUA process</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the maximum amount of RAM in megabytes per process usable by Lua. By default it is zero which means unlimited. It is important to set a limit to ensure that a bug in a script will not result in the system running out of memory.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.spreadChecks</id>
        <label>Spread checks</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Add some randomness in the check interval between 0 and +/- 50%. A value between 2 and 5 seems to show good results. The default value is 0 (disabled).]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.bogusProxyEnabled</id>
        <label>Enable old bogus PROXY v2 implementation</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[A bug in the PROXY protocol v2 implementation was present in HAProxy up to version 2.1. Enabling this option reverts this old buggy behaviour.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.customOptions</id>
        <label>Custom options</label>
        <type>textbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[These lines will be added to the global settings of to the HAProxy configuration file.<br/><div class="text-info"><b>NOTE:</b> The syntax will not be checked, use at your own risk!</div>]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <label>SSL settings</label>
        <type>header</type>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.ocspUpdateEnabled</id>
        <label>Automatic OCSP updates</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enable automatic OCSP response updates. Each OCSP response will be updated at least once an hour, and even more frequently if a given OCSP response has an expire date earlier than this one hour limit.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.ocspUpdateMinDelay</id>
        <label>Minimum OCSP Interval</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the minimum interval (in seconds) between two automatic updates of the same OCSP response.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.ocspUpdateMaxDelay</id>
        <label>Maximum OCSP Interval</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the maximum interval (in seconds) between two automatic updates of the same OCSP response.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <label>SSL default settings</label>
        <type>header</type>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.ssl_defaultsEnabled</id>
        <label>Enabled</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Enable global SSL default values.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.ssl_minVersion</id>
        <label>Minimum SSL Version</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[This option enforces use of the specified version (or higher) on SSL connections.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.ssl_maxVersion</id>
        <label>Maximum SSL Version</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[This option enforces use of the specified version (or lower) on SSL connections.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.ssl_cipherList</id>
        <label>Cipher List</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[It sets the default string describing the list of cipher algorithms ("cipher suite") that are negotiated during the SSL/TLS handshake up to TLSv1.2.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.ssl_cipherSuites</id>
        <label>Cipher Suites</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[It sets the default string describing the list of cipher algorithms ("cipher suite") that are negotiated during the SSL/TLS handshake for TLSv1.3.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.ssl_bindOptions</id>
        <label>Bind options</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <style>tokenize</style>
        <allownew>true</allownew>
        <sortable>true</sortable>
        <help><![CDATA[Used to enforce or disable certain SSL options.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <label>HTTP/2 Performance</label>
        <type>header</type>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.h2_initialWindowSize</id>
        <label>Initial window size</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the default value for the HTTP/2 initial window size, on both incoming and outgoing connections. The default value is 65536.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.h2_initialWindowSizeOutgoing</id>
        <label>Initial window size (outgoing)</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the HTTP/2 initial window size for outgoing connections, which is the number of bytes the server can respond to before waiting for an acknowledgment from HAProxy.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.h2_initialWindowSizeIncoming</id>
        <label>Initial window size (incoming)</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the HTTP/2 initial window size for incoming connections, which is the number of bytes the client can upload before waiting for an acknowledgment from HAProxy.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.h2_maxConcurrentStreams</id>
        <label>Max concurrent streams</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the default HTTP/2 maximum number of concurrent streams per connection (i.e. the number of outstanding requests on a single connection). The default value is 100.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.h2_maxConcurrentStreamsOutgoing</id>
        <label>Max concurrent streams (outgoing)</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the HTTP/2 maximum number of concurrent streams per outgoing connection (i.e. the number of outstanding requests on a single connection to a server).]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>haproxy.general.tuning.h2_maxConcurrentStreamsIncoming</id>
        <label>Max concurrent streams (incoming)</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Sets the HTTP/2 maximum number of concurrent streams per incoming connection (i.e. the number of outstanding requests on a single connection from a client).]]></help>
    </field>
</form>
